# **Lucas Gabriel Rubo**

lucasrubo1@gmail.com +55 19 994019804 | Valinhos SP, 13272-000

#### **About**

I'm a 22-year-old Junior Developer. I have the ability to work on multiple tasks at the same time, keeping myself organized and focused to deliver the activities. I constantly seek to improve my skills and knowledge in technology to contribute to the projects I work on.

I hold a degree in Computer Science and aim to gain practical experience in the market and expand my knowledge in the field of development. I am eager to contribute with my technical ability and commitment to teamwork to achieve challenging goals. Thank you for the opportunity to present my profile and I am available for further clarification.

### **Academic Education**

Computer Science at UNIVERSIDADE PAULISTA

Bachelor's degree: 2019 - 2022

Systems Development at SENAI ZERBINI

Technician: 2017 - 2019

## **Professional History**

▶ Junior Developer at NB41

out.2019 a fev.2021 e jan.2023 So far

As a developer, I specialize in developing and modifying front-end and PHP systems. I possess expertise in creating WordPress websites and maintaining/creating databases to ensure optimal performance.

▶ Development Intern at IBM

out.2021 a out.2022

**Skills** 

I worked in CI/CD focusing on test automation and pipelines to ensure continuous delivery. I created pipelines, tests, documentation, and scripts to improve processes.

#### HTML JavaScript Photoshop Python Intermediate Advanced Advanced Intermediate **CSS** C++ Node.js Excel Advanced Intermediate Advanced Intermediate PHP **PowerPoint** Laravel JAVA Intermediate Intermediate Basic Basic Jenkins English Word MySql Intermediate Intermediate Intermediate (C1) Intermediate